NASIR TOMLIN

Email: nasirt@g.clemson.edu Personal: nas.tomlin@gmail.com

Phone: 843-214-7753

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Hardworking, reliable, and someone who cooperates well in a team setting. Years of experience with coding, data mapping, and problem-solving. Able to adapt to any environment with a positive impact. An eagerness to learn and grow for career improvement.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Tiger Alliance Program Ambassador | Clemson University

August 2022 - Present

Planned and implemented program activities for high school students.

Provided structured educational and recreational opportunities for students.

Mentor High School students with a path to college.

Organized and led tours of the campus and various group activities.

CONNECTIONS Mentor | Clemson University

August 2022 - Present

Mentor first-year students throughout their college experience.

Host study sessions to improve academic success.

Meet collectively to create campus activities.

Host on-campus events.

Undergrads Moving | Clemson University

May 2021 – Present

Assisted customers during moves with excellent customer service.

Work as a team to complete jobs efficiently.

Showcased great leadership skills to accomplish the end goal.

Sales Associate | Lowes

May 2021 - Present

Helping customers find the products they need while providing general assistance.

Process orders, deliveries, and loaded tickets.

Forklift Operator

Sales Associate | Finish Line

May 2020 - August 2020

Assist customers with product details.

Perform cash and credit transactions at the time of purchase.

Organize the shoe wall and stockroom to maintain store cleanliness.

Help increase sales throughout the store.

Administrative Assistant | A.L.L. SERVICES, LLC

August 2016 - May 2020

Answers phone calls.

Created and faxed invoices.

Carries out administrative duties such as filing, typing, and copying.

EDUCATION

Clemson University

August 2020 - Present

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | Minor: Cybersecurity

- CU Cyber
- Tiger Alliance Ambassador
- CONNECTIONS MENTOR
- Brother2Brother
- Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity Inc.

Trident Technical College

August 2019 - May 2020

• Dual enrollment: Attended one year (4 courses)

Fort Dorchester High School

August 2019 – May 2020

• High School Diploma

Certifications

- Microsoft Office
- GIS Pro
- Data Visualization
- Forklift Operator

Skills

- Updating, Designing, and editing website content
- Ethical Hacking
- Leadership Experience
- Microsoft Office 365
- C, C++, Java, SQL
- Database experience
- Management Experience

Community Service

- Helping Hands
- Campus Clean-up
- Operation Christmas Child
- Lowcounty Food Bank